Guide to the Melanie Dornier photographs, 2013-2016 RL.11523
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 2013-2016
  - Punch My Face: Women's Boxing in India, 2013-2016
    - Womans' talk, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2015 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0086)
      Meena is sitting in her bedroom with her best friends Poonam and Suchi. During this time the men are eating in the living room.
    - Meena, Poonam and Sunil, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2015 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0087)
      In her living room, Meena is having a laugh with her best friend Poonam and her husband Sunil.
    - Ponytail, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0088)
      In her living room, Meena is getting ready to go outside.
    - Sickness, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0089)
      In the house, Meena is sick and her husband, Sunil is taking care of her.
    - Doctor's appointment, private hospital, Karnal, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0090)
      Meena and her husband Sunil are consulting a gynecologist at the early stage of her pregnancy.
    - Family portrait, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2014 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0091)
      Meena, her husband Sunil and their 18 months daughter KuKee are sitting in the bedroom chatting.
    - Anger, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0092)
      Meena is threatening to slap her three year-old daughter KuKee.
    - Meena Kumari, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2013 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0093)
      In her living room, Meena is waiting for the babysitter to look after her nine month-old daughter, while she has to report for duty in uniform.
    - Meena Kumari, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0094)
      In her living room, Meena is playing with her daughter after her police duty.
    - Feeding, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0095)
      Meena is giving a glass of rose-flavored milk to her daughter KuKee before to dropping her to her nanny.
    - Dressing, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2013 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0096)
      In her bedroom, Meena is dressing up in uniform.
    - Closet, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2013 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0097)
      Meena's shoes closet.
    - Meena Kumari, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0098)
      In her house, Meena is posing in her police uniform of Sub Inspector in front of Lord Shiva's temple.
    - Police duty, Rewari District, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0099)
      During the Panchayat's (equivalent of mayor) election, Meena is on duty to ensure order in villages.
    - Police training, Karnal, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0100)
      Meena is learning how to make a traffic fine.
    - Meena Kumari, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0101)
      Meena is feeding herself with milk before going on duty.
    - Pictures and icons, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0102)
      On the shelves of Meena's house, there are icons of Sai Baba, the goddess Durga and pictures of Meena's husband and father in military uniform.
    - Meena's buffalo, Mundi, Rewari District, Haryana, India, 2014 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0103)
      It is a portrait of Meena's mother, Saraswaki Devi Kumari with relatives in front of Meena's buffalo in the family village.
    - Harvest, Mundi, Rewari District, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0104)
      Meena is helping her mother to harvest the family's field.
    - Harvest, Mundi, Rewari district, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0105)
    - Picnic, Mundi, Rewari district, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0106)
      Meena is sharing a meal with her mother and daughter during the lunchtime of the harvest.
    - Portrait of Meena and her daughter, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0107)
      In the living room, Meena and her daughter KuKee are sitting in the sofa looking at a book.
    - Packing, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0108)
      In the living room, Meena is packing a backpack to spend a night out in the Ashram of Marajah Rajinder Singh with her daughter Kukee.
    - Dressing, Police quarter, Madhuban, Haryana, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0109)
      Meena is getting ready, putting her bangles on to assist at the public show of Marajah Rajinder Singh in North Delhi.
    - Praying, Marajah Rajinder Singh's Ashram, New Delhi, India, 2016 (Box 2, Image RL.11523-P-0110)
      Meena and her daughter Kukee, seated on the floor, are praying in the Ashram waiting for Marajah Rajinder Singh.